Guide to the Benno C. Schmidt, Jr., President of Yale University, Inauguration Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Benno C. Schmidt, Jr., president of Yale University, inauguration records
1986-1986
RU 374
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
4
The records consist of newspaper clippings and greetings documenting the inauguration of Benno C. Schmidt, Jr. as president of Yale.
Yale University. President's Office
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 2-A (YRG 2-A), Records of the Yale president's office.
Conditions Governing Access
Access prohibited for 35 years from the completion date of tenure of the University officer responsible for the creation of the records.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of newspaper clippings and greetings documenting the inauguration of Benno C. Schmidt, Jr. as president of Yale.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
College presidents -- Inauguration; Schmidt, Benno C., 1942-; Yale University -- Presidents; Yale University. President's Office
- Inaugural greetings sent to Benno C. Schmidt as president of Yale University, 1986; Series I
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until January 1, 2021.
  - Inaugural Greetings, 1986
    - Alberta, University of (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - American Philosophical Society (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Arizona, University of (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Brooklyn College (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Brandeis University (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Case Western Reserve University
      General
      See: Oversize box 3, folder 30
    - Chicago, University of (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Colorado, University of (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Columbia University
      See: Oversize box 3, folder 31
    - Connecticut, University of (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Dalhousie University (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Dartmouth College
      See: Oversize box 3, folder 32
    - Delaware, University of (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Edinburgh, University of (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Emory University (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Florida, University of (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Harvard University
      See: Oversize box 3, folder 33
    - Howard University
      See: Oversize box 3, folder 34
    - Iowa State University (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Kentucky, University of (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Maine at Orono, University of (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - McMaster University (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology
      See: Oversize box 3, folder 35
    - Michigan, University of (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - New England Conservatory of Music (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Northeastern University
      See: Oversize box 3, folder 36
    - Oberlin College (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Pennsylvania, University of (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Pittsburgh, University of (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Princeton University (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Queens College at Kingston (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Smith College (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - United States Military Academy
      See: Oversize box 3, folder 37
    - Vanderbilt University (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Vassar College (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Virginia, University of (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Oversize
      - Case Western Reserve University (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Columbia University (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Dartmouth College (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Harvard University (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Howard University (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Northeastern University (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - United States Military Academy (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Newsclippings documenting the inauguration of Benno C. Schmidt, 1986; Accession 1997-A-066
  - Newsclippings (3) of the inauguration of Benno C. Schmidt, 1986 (Box 1)
- Assorted materials concerning Benno C. Schmidt's inauguration, 1986; Accession 2002-A-135 (Box 1)
  No inventory available.